Born leader.
The Boss Baby is a animation, comedy, family film directed by Tom McGrath.
A story about how a new baby's arrival impacts a family, told from the point of view of a
delightfully unreliable narrator, a wildly imaginative 7 year old named Tim.
Theodore Templeton (voice), played by Alec Baldwin.
Francis E. Francis (voice), played by Steve Buscemi.
Tim Templeton (voice), played by Miles Bakshi.
Ted Templeton (voice), played by Jimmy Kimmel.
Janice Templeton (voice), played by Lisa Kudrow.
Narrator / Older Tim Templeton (voice), played by Tobey Maguire.
The Boss Baby is a 2017 American animated spy comedy film starring
Alec Baldwin as the voice of the titular character.
Loosely based on the 2010 picture book The Boss Baby by Marla Frazee, it was
directed by Tom McGrath and written by Michael McCullers.
Produced by DreamWorks Animation, it is the first
film in The Boss Baby franchise.
The film follows a boy helping his baby brother who is a secret agent
in the war for adults' love between babies and puppies.
The Boss Baby premiered at the Miami International Film Festival on March 12, 2017,
and was released in the United States on March 31 by 20th Century Fox.
The film received mixed reviews from critics and was a commercial success,
grossing $528 million worldwide against a $125 million budget.
The film was nominated for Best Animated Feature at the 90th
Academy Awards, the Annie Awards, and the Golden Globes.
The success of the film spawned a franchise, including two television series, The Boss Baby: Back in
Business and The Boss Baby: Back In the Crib, and a sequel film, The Boss Baby: Family Business.
The film explores themes of baby, villain, family
relationships, puppy, sibling rivalry.
The tone is lighthearted.